杰森 · 兰斯托夫: 现在 FX 道具正在采集我们想要的东西,
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Now that FX
prop is picking up what we want,
而是做我们想做的事。
it's doing the things
that we wanted to do.
这太棒了，这正是我们想要的。
This is great,
this is exactly what we're after.
但是有一些奇怪的事情，对吗？
But there are a couple weird things,
right?
就像我们得到了这个边缘，而这个边缘来自身体。
Like we've got this margin and
that comes from the body.
因此，如果我们想覆盖这个主题 UI，实际上它并不是为处理全局而构建的
So if we wanna override that theme UI
isn't actually built to handle global
风格。
styles.
这是一件你必须要小心的事情，因为如果你加上
And this is something that you have to be
kinda careful about because if you add
全局风格,
global styles,
全局样式可以冲突 CSS 的一大挑战是理解范围。
global styles can conflict one of the big
challenges of CSS is understanding scope.
当你把事情放到全球范围内,
And when you start putting
things in the global scope,
在整个团队中扩展，会变得非常具有挑战性。
it can become really challenging
as it scales out across the team.
所以当你应用全局样式的时候，你要非常谨慎。
So you wanna be very sparing about
when you apply global styles.
我认为有一件事是可以接受的，那就是移除
One thing that I think is kind of a
generally acceptable thing to do is remove
主体，边距和填充，这样东西可以去的视口的边缘。
the body, margin and padding, so that
things can go to the edge of the viewport.
所以，为了做到这一点，我们要跳回到我们的布局和
So, to do that we're gonna
hop back into our layout and
我们将从 emotion / core 中引入 Global。
we're going to import
Global from emotion/core.
在情感 / 核心方面，我们可以定义一些全局风格,
And in emotion/core we're able to just
kind of define some global styles,
真是太好了。
which is really nice.
所以我们就这么做吧，我要做全局风格。
So let's just do that,
I'm gonna do global styles.
我想把主体设置为0。
And I want to set the body
to have a margin of 0.
现在它到了屏幕的边缘。
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: And
now it goes to the edge of the screen.
所以再一次，尽量少用，但是这是一个修复诸如身体边缘之类的东西的方便的方法。
So again, use that sparingly, but it is a
handy way to fix things like body margin.